<GodCards>
    <God>
        <Name>Apollo</Name>
        <Effects>CanSwitch</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You can switch position with opponent workers</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>Your worker may move into an opponent worker's space (using normal movement rules) and
            force their worker to the space yours just vacated (swapping their position).</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Artemis</Name>
        <Effects>CanMoveTwice</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You can move twice, but no turning back</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>Your worker may move one additional time, but not back to the space he started on.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Athena</Name>
        <Effects>CantMoveUp</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>If you move up, they can't</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>If one of your worker moved up on your last turn, opponent workers cannot move up
            this turn.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Atlas</Name>
        <Effects>CanBuildDome</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You can build domes at any level</DisplayEffects>
        <Description> Your worker may build a dome at any level including the ground.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Demeter</Name>
        <Effects>CanBuildTwiceDifferent</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You can build twice, but not on the same space</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>Your worker may build one additional time, but not on the same space.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Hephaestus</Name>
        <Effects>CanBuildTwice</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You can build twice in the same space (not dome)</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>Your worker may build one additional block (not dome) on top of your first block.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Minotaur</Name>
        <Effects>CanPush</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You can push opponent workers</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>Your worker may move into an opponent worker's space (using normal movement rules),
            if the next space in the same direction is unoccupied. Their worker is forced into that space (regardless of its level).</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Pan</Name>
        <Effects>MoveDownToWin</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You can win moving down two or more levels</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>You also win if your worker moves down two or more levels.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Prometheus</Name>
        <Effects>BuildBeforeMove</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>If you don't move up, you may build both before and after moving</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>If your worker does not move up, it may build both before and after moving.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Chronus</Name>
        <Effects>CompleteTowersObserver</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You can also win with five complete towers</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>You also win when there are at least five complete towers on the board.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Hestia</Name>
        <Effects>BuildTwiceNoPerimeter</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You can build twice but the second build cannot be on the perimeter</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>Your worker may build one additional time. The additional build cannot be on a perimeter space.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Medusa</Name>
        <Effects>PetrifyOpponents</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You petrify your opponents</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>If any of your opponent's workers occupy lower neighboring spaces, replace them all with
            blocks and remove them from the game.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Triton</Name>
        <Effects>CanMoveMultipleTimesPerimeter</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>If you move onto perimeter, you can move again</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>Each time your worker moves onto a perimeter space (ground or block), it may immediately move again.</Description>
    </God>
    <God>
        <Name>Zeus</Name>
        <Effects>CanBuildBelow</Effects>
        <DisplayEffects>You can build below yourself</DisplayEffects>
        <Description>Your worker may build under itself in its current space, forcing it up one level.
            You do not win by forcing yourself up to the third level.</Description>
    </God>
</GodCards>
